utube.com 2010-05-27

# Privacy Policy

**Dear UTUBE Customer,**

UTUBE recognizes your expectation for the responsible use and protection of your information and your right to privacy. To this end, we will maintain standards to reasonably ensure that your information is private and secure at all times. This notice will describe how your information is used, protected and the benefits such use provides to you.

"You" or "Your" means you as a participant in or as a user of the UTUBE program. "We", "Our" or "Us" means UTUBE. "Our site" means the UTUBE®.

All information transmitted, printed or otherwise submitted to The UTUBE via this website shall be deemed to be the property of UTUBE and shall be free to use such information for any lawful purpose as detailed herein.

We reserve the right to release such information to law enforcement or other governmental officials as we, in our sole and absolute discretion, deem necessary to comply with the law.

**Contents of the Notice:**

  1. _Collected Information._
  2. _Use of Data Collected._
  3. _Disclosure of Data to Third Parties._
  4. _Your Opt-Out Rights._
  5. _Your Rights To Your Personal Data._
  6. _We Do Not Intend To Collect Data From Children._
  7. _Our Right To Contact You._
  8. _Our Right To Change._
  9. _Our Contact Information._

**1) Collected information.**

We automatically collect and/or track the following:

  1. Web page http headers (home server domain names, IP address, type of client computer, and type of Web browser);
  2. Information knowingly provided by you through on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and or other entries, such as email addresses, personal, financial or demographic information;
  3. Information, user specific or aggregate, on what pages our visitors access;
  4. The e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with UTUBE via e-mail.

**2) Use of data collected.**

We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience with UTUBE and to enable us to present content we think might interest you. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our web site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online.

We only share personal identification information with other companies or individuals outside of UTUBE in the following limited circumstances:

Third Party Service-Providers: Utube.com may from time to time share email addresses and other personal identification information with third parties to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending informational emails about our products and services. In these cases, Utube.com uses only trusted partners who have entered into non-disclosure agreements prohibiting use or dissemination of personal identification information and that meet the requirements set out in the Security section below.

**Third Party Marketers:** We may share personal identification information you supply to us to selected third parties for direct marketing purposes, unless you request for this information not to be disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes using the opt out below or you have previously opted out from your personal identification information being disclosed to third parties for marketing purposes. These businesses may include, providers of direct marketing services via telemarketing, e-mail marketing, direct mail, SMS messaging and other types of direct marketing.

**Other Third Parties:** We may share personal identification information you supply to us to other selected third parties, including providers of applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation. 

**3) Disclosure of data to third parties.**

If you choose to provide personal information, it will be used for the following purposes:

  1. as required by law; and 
  2. for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest. We reserve the right to share, rent, consign, or otherwise disclose data we collect to third parties, including from UTUBE. Any third party we share, rent, consign, or otherwise disclose data to will be prescreened by us, determined by us to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest.

**4) Your opt-out rights.**

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and or our partners by not submitting your information. We also allow you to remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondences to you. You can opt-out and/or remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to [help-contact@utube.com](mailto:help-contact@utube.com) and requesting your profile be deleted.

**5) Your rights to your personal data.**

Upon request via e-mail, we will provide you a summary of personal information retained by us. We will only send your personal records to your e-mail address or postal address we have on file for you. You may modify, correct, change, or update your personal record or remove your personal record from our database by sending your request in writing via email to:

_[help-contact@utube.com](mailto:help-contact@utube.com)_ and stating your request.

**6) We do not intend to collect data from children.**

The information and services provided us or our affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children (under 18 years old). No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside UTUBE.

**7) Our right to contact you.**

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.

**8) Our right to change.**

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our site.

**9) Our contact information.**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our website, you can contact us via email sent to: _[help-contact@utube.com](mailto:help-contact@utube.com)_.

BY VISITING THIS WEBSITE AND REQUESTING INFORMATION, PRODUCTS OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEBSITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

PLEASE NOTE: THIS PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. WE DO NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE.

This policy describes the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of _UTUBE_ , its parents, subsidiaries and registered d/b/a companies (Collectively Referred herein after as "Company") and all related websites owned or registered to Company and applies to Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Company on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various Third Party websites, and (c) to Company's other information collection, including the acquisition of customer information from third parties. Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications.

By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms and Conditions pertaining to the use of the website. Your use of the website and any personal information you provide via the website or through other official Company contact remains subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the applicable Terms and Conditions for use of the site or services and products contained thereon.

By providing us with your personal information on our website or in the course of using our services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Data and Sensitive Personal Data, and any other data we acquire about you from third-party service providers in the process of evaluating you for a loan, to companies outside the EU, including but not limited to, other consumer credit lenders and their affiliates. 

Information Collection, Use, and Dissemination practices:   
This policy applies to Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Company on its, (a) websites, including all its parent companies, divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to Company's other information collection, including the transfer of opt-in customer lists from third parties, or the use of customer opt-in lists from third parties. Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications. 

**1\. Collection of Information.**

**1.1. User Direct Information:**   
Each time you provide transmit information via the Website, Company may obtain and collect personally identifiable information provided by you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, social security number, credit card information, and telephone number. You may also provide us with information that, when combined with personally identifiable information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, including but not limited to your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level (collectively referred to as "personal information"). If you choose to access our website, use our services or purchase our products, we may require you to provide personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the site. 

**1.2. Survey Information:**   
Company may collect information from you when you voluntarily complete a Company survey, order form, or a registration page either online by using the internet, offline by providing this information through the mail, in person or using a telephone. This information may be collected by surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties. This method of collection is collectively known as a "Survey." In such Surveys, Company or a third party may ask you to provide personal identifiable information including your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. Company may also collect such information concerning you from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from the Websites. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and you are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Company or a third party. 

**1.3. Third Party Information:**   
Company may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and Company subsequently acquires the information from the third party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the you may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, Company seeks assurances from the third party that you agreed to provide and have such information acquired by Company. If you did not give express permission, or you would like to remove your permission, you may suppress all of your information by sending notification to us at help-contact@utube.com **.**

**1.4. Other Methods of Collecting Personal Information:**   
Other occasions when Company obtains information from you include (1) your claiming a prize or seeking to redeem an offer by Company or by a third party, (2) your requests for assistance through Company's customer service department, and (3) when you voluntarily subscribe to a Company service or newsletter. 

**1.5. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology:**   
Company currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, Company may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future.   
**(a) Cookies:**   
"Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at [http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/). In order to use all of the features and functionality of Company's websites, you need to accept cookies.   
**(b) Web Beacons:**   
A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Company to track certain websites you visit. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Company also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Company's database.   
**(c) IP Addresses:**   
Company automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.  
**(d) Computer Profiles:**   
Company may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, Company may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you.   
**(e) Data Analysis:**   
Data Analysis technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of Company.   
**(f) New Technology:**   
The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, Company strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology. 

**1.6. No Information Collected from Children:**   
Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

**1.7. Credit Card Information:**   
Company may, in certain instances, collect credit card numbers and related information when an individual places an order from Company. When the credit card information is submitted to Company, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Company will use the credit card information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the credit card information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. 

**2\. Use of Individual Information.**

**2.1 General Use.** The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how Company currently uses Individual Information, but Company may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, Company may update this policy from time to time. Company may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

**2.2 Email and Unsubscribe Policy**. Company uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. Company may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. This site allows visitors to unsubscribe from this offer so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.  
Company's unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by Company on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of Third Parties and your personal information may still be shared with Third Parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends.  
You should also note that unsubscribing from Company's electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the subscriber's information from any Third Party business associates and licensees of the data. Since Third Party associates and licensee partners maintain separate databases from Company, and you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

**2.3 Content of Email Messages**. In certain commercial email messages sent by Company, an Advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to Company. The "Subject:" line of Company email messages will usually contain a line provided from the Advertiser to Company.

**2.4 Solicited Email.** Company only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Websites to receive email from Company or from a third-party consumer credit lender with whom Company shares information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, or to individuals who have agreed on a Third Party website to receive email from Third Parties. As such, Company does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, United States statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Company 's email messages.

**2.5 Targeted Advertising.** Company uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Company uses Technology Information to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and Company attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Company may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, SMS, text messaging and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

**2.6 Telemarketing.** Company uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones. By registering and using this Site, You acknowledge that the processing of your individual information may involve the transfer of such Individual information from within or outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries within or outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as stringent as that within the European Union. We may use individual information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 

**2.7 Wireless Addresses.** If the e-mail address you provide to Company is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from Company or its business associates (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the unsubscribe portion of this policy). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages. 

**2.8 Short Message Service.** Company may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. Company will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. Company may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.  
You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. We may also access the content of your account and wireless account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and service-related complaints.   
Company may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. Company may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services. Company may share aggregated and non personal information with third parties business associates. When Company uses business associates to assist Company in processing your personal information, Company requires that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Company may also share information with third parties, including but not limited to, when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.  
You may remove your information from Company's database. If you remove your information from Company's database it will no longer be used by Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Company or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to help-contact@utube.com or by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.

**2.9 Use of Technology Information.** Company uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Company's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps Company to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Company can target advertising and promotions to them.

**2.10 Profiles of Individuals.** Company uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.

**2.11 Storage of Individual Information.** Company stores the Individual Information in a database on its' computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Company's control. Not withstanding such measures, Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

**3\. Use of Personal Information.**   
Company uses your personal information in the following 3 ways: Customer Service; Sharing your personal information with a consumer credit lender where applicable, Marketing; and Complying with Legal Process. 

**3.1. Customer Service:**   
The following section informs you of how the Company will use your personal information. 

**3.2 Credit Lenders:**   
By providing us with your personal information on the website or in the course of using our services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Data and Sensitive Personal Data, and any other data we acquire about you from third-party service providers in the process of evaluating you for a loan to consumer credit lenders and their affiliates. These companies may be located outside the EU. 

**3.3. Marketing:**   
Company will use your personal information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of Company and its affiliates and subsidiaries to send information to you about additional goods or services that may be of interest to you. In addition, Company will disclose your personal information to third party agents and independent contractors to help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts and to share with other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing. You may have no relationship with these other companies. 

**3.4. Complying with Legal Process:**   
Company will use or disclose your personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with Company. Company will use and disclose your personal information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of Company , its owners, or those of Company 's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your personal information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Company's acceptable use policy, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes. 

**3.5. Order Fulfillment:**   
Company will transfer your personal information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from such third party while using Company's websites or when responding to offers provided by Company. 

**3.6. Data Summary:**   
Company may share or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons. 

**3.7. Third Parties:**   
Company may provide your personal information to third parties with whom they have a business relationship for the purposes of securing the services and products you have requested or provide you with additional marketing materials from which you may choose additional products or services. 

**3.8. Our right to Contact You** By using our website, you consent to Company, or a consumer credit lender with whom Company shares information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, to contact you by phone or email for marketing purposes or regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.

**4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.**

**4.1. Advertiser cookies and web beacons:**   
Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the websites and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control the use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you. 

**4.2. Links:**   
The websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

**4.3. Affiliations/Merger/Sale:**   
Company further reserves the right to disclose, transfer or share your personal information to companies who are affiliated with Company in Company's sole discretion. If Company changes ownership through an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of business status, it reserves the right to transfer or assign the right to use your Personal Information collected from the Website.

**5\. Foreign use of the Website.** To the extent that you are accessing the Website while domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the Personal Information you are providing Company is collected and stored in the United States and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States. You further consent to the transfer of your Personal Data and Sensitive Personal Data, and any other data we acquire about you from third-party service providers in the process of evaluating you for a loan, to companies outside the EU, including but not limited to, other consumer credit lenders and their affiliates. 

**6\. Fraud Prevention:  
**If false or inaccurate information is provided, including in relation to a person�s identity and fraud is identified, details about this information, including customer Personal Data, will be passed to fraud prevention agencies. Law enforcement agencies may access and use this information. We and other organizations may also access and use this information to prevent fraud and money laundering, for example when: checking details on applications for credit and credit related and other facilities; managing credit and credit related accounts or other facilities; recovering debt; checking details on proposals and claims for all types of insurance; and checking details of job applicants and employees. For further details of the relevant fraud prevention agencies please contact us as described in this Privacy Policy.
